■
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
翻譯：文人騷客賽太公  粘人騷貨YY貓  貓中之王  不再獨醉的芝士
校對：文人騷客賽太公  粘人騷貨YY貓  總監   YY貓
后期：灰灰是菇涼   時間軸：YY貓
生活大爆炸
第七季  第十三集
《生活大爆炸》前情回顧
Previously on The Big Bang Theory:
這只是一點小挫折
This is just a minor setback.
這不是  明白嗎
No, it's not, okay?
我已經離家拼搏十年了
I've been out here for, like, ten years.
我依然一無所有
I have nothing to show for it.
你有我啊
Well, you have me.
我的確擁有你
I do have you.
萊納德·霍夫斯塔德
Leonard Hofstadter,
你愿意娶我嗎
will you marry me?
你剛才那一聲是在猶豫嗎
Did you seriously just say, "Um..."?
事到如今
-這太過分了  -我明白
- It's an outrage. - I know.
大學的高層覺得他們想干嘛就能干嘛
The university-- they think they can do whatever they want.
我們只能乖乖任由擺布
We just have to sit there and take it.
別老拽著這事不放了  謝爾頓
You need to let it go, Sheldon.
我沒日沒夜地為他們干活  卻落得如此下場
You work tirelessly for someone, and this is what you get.
我的老天啊
Oh, my God!
他們就是讓你把年假用掉而已
They're just making you use your vacation days!
可我不想放假
But I don't want a vacation.
我不想輕視你心靈受到的創傷
Okay, listen, I don't mean to diminish what you're going through,
但我現在真的沒心思
but I'm a little distracted right now.
又是因為那事啊
Oh, this again?
不就是佩妮求了婚  你沒答應嘛
So, Penny proposed, you didn't say yes,
所以現在你天天發愁到底會不會失去她
and now you think you may have lost her love forever.
這破事怎么比得上我被人
How does this compare to me being forced
逼迫放假來得慘啊
to relax for a few days?
-完全比不上  -就是嘛
- It doesn't! - Thank you!
我要去跟佩妮談談
I'm gonna go talk to Penny.
我要回家穿上我最舒服的睡衣
I'm going to go inside, put on my coziest pajamas,
蜷在床上看本好書
curl up with a good book
等待這場噩夢的結束
and wait for this nightmare to be over.
佩妮
Penny.
抱歉  情不自禁
Sorry.
抱歉沒回你短信
Hey. Look, I'm sorry I didn't text you back.
我只是需要點時間想想
I just needed some time to think.
-沒事  -來  進來吧
- Okay. - Here. Come in.
如果你是想要分手  就說出來吧
Look, if you want to break up, just say it.
-萊納德...  -別別別  我收回那句話
- Leonard... - No, no, no, no. I take it back.
千萬別分手  恨我就好  別離開我
Don't say it. Just-just hate me, but stay with me.
反正我爸媽也這樣
It worked for my parents.
聽我說  我沒想要跟你分手
Listen, I don't want to break up with you.
那就好
Oh. O-Okay.
很好  很好
Good, good.
不介意我落兩滴男兒淚吧
So, it's cool if I cry a little?
要我就不會這么做
Yeah, I probably wouldn't.
同意
Yeah.
你昨晚的做法是正確的
Look, you did the right thing last night.
我當時腦子不清楚
I was a mess.
當時我因為事業不順  內心嚴重受挫
I was just frustrated because my career is going nowhere.
我理解  我也想你知道
Look, I get it, and I want you to know
無論你想做什么事  我都支持你
that I support whatever you want to do.
那就好  因為我在想
Great, because I've been thinking,
如果我真想要演員事業能成功
if I really want this acting thing to work,
我就得身心完全投入
I need to focus all my energy on it.
為了做到真正投入
And to do that,
我決定辭芝士蛋糕工廠的服務員工作
I should quit waitressing at The Cheesecake Factory.
-這是個大改變啊  -我知道
- That-That's a big step. - I know.
所以在你做任何沖動的...
So, you know, before making any rash...
-我已經辭職了  -那我也支持你
- I already quit. - And I support you!
-好嘛  帶我跟你去上班  -不行
- Come on, take me to work with you. - No.
-你在放假  -求你了
- You're on vacation. - Please.
萬一今天科學界有重大突破
What if there's a big breakthrough in science today
我卻錯過無法見證呢
and I'm not there to see it?
你真的覺得你如果不在  科學界能有什么
Do you really think there's gonna be a breakthrough
重大突破嗎
without you there to do it?
當然不會有  這是陷阱題
No. I was just tricking you.
再會
Bye.
萊納德  等等
Leonard, wait!
-帶我一起去  -不行
- Take me with you.- No!
-求你了  -就是不行
- Please. - No!
抱歉  我就是要跟著你
Too bad. I'm coming with you.
-謝爾頓  停  -但是...
- Oh, Sheldon, stay! - But...
乖乖待著
I said stay!
我要去上班了
I'm going to work.
不許跟著我
Do not follow me.
斯圖爾特
Hey, Stuart.
-你好啊  -抱歉  我嚇到你了嗎
- Hey. - Sorry. Did I startle you?
沒關系  這時間所有客人都會嚇到我
Yes, but at this point, pretty much any customer does.
你要買什么
What can I do for you?
我需要你幫個忙
Well, I need a little help.
今早我不小心弄壞了霍華德的一本漫畫書
I accidentally destroyed one of Howard's comic books this morning,
所以我想買一本來替換
and I was hoping I could replace it.
發生了什么事
Wow. What happened?
蝙蝠俠被我的燙發棒給虐了
Batman got his ass kicked by my curling iron.
可別把這個秘密告訴謎語人
Well, don't let The Riddler know that.
蝙蝠俠敵手
這是個漫畫哏啦
It's a comic book joke.
也可能不是哏吧
Or maybe it's not.
你還有這本書嗎
Do you have this one?
這本書市面上很少見了
Uh, well, it's-it's pretty rare.
我需要幾天時間找一下
Can you give me a few days to track it down?
我還希望能在華仔下班
Ooh, I was kind of hoping to get it
回家之前就把書換掉
before Howie comes home from work.
干嘛這么著急
Oh. What's the hurry?
他平時就愛念叨
Well, he's always saying
讓我用燙發棒的時候多注意點
I should be more careful with my curling iron,
要是讓他發現
and it seems like a dangerous precedent
他也有說對的時候就慘了
to let him think he can be right.
我盡力而為吧
Well, I'll do what I can,
但我可不敢打包票一定能找到
but I can't make any promises.
其實我在制藥公司工作呢
You know, I do work at a pharmaceutical company.
如果你今天能幫我找到書
If you can make this happen today,
我就能幫你搞點抗焦慮
I can hook you up with anxiety medication,
-和抗抑郁的藥  -是嗎
- antidepressants. - Really?
那你有這些藥嗎
Do you have any of these?
鼠腦君  你好嗎
Hello, Mr. Rat Brain.
沒了身體的其他部分
Not so bitey without the rest of the rat
現在沒法咬我了吧
to back us up now, are we?
有人嗎
Anybody home?
你倆來干什么
Hey, what brings you guys here?
我們要去吃午飯
Well, we were just on our way to lunch
順道看看你想不想一起去
and wanted to see if you'd like to join.
為什么
Why?
因為這周謝爾頓不上班
Because Sheldon's not here this week,
你們就覺得我沒有別人陪伴了嗎
and you don't think I have any other options?
開玩笑的  我拿上包就走
I'm just kidding. I'll get my purse.
艾米  我
Hi, Amy. I... Oh.
抱歉  我不知道你有客人在
I'm sorry. I didn't know you had any company.
沒關系
That's okay.
伯特  這是霍華德和拉杰什
Uh, Bert, this is Howard and Rajesh.
這位是Bert
Guys, this is Bert.
-很高興見到你  -你好
- Hey. Good to see you. - Hey.
我是想過來給你看看
Anyway, I wanted to show you
我們在實驗室弄出來的石英晶體
this tourmalinated quartz that we got in the lab.
真漂亮
This is so pretty.
-伯特在地質系工作  -沒錯
- Bert works for the geology department. - Yeah.
你們知道地質學家和邦·喬飛的共同點是什么嗎
You know what, uh, geologists and Bon Jovi have in common?
你們都喜歡石頭[搖滾]嗎
You're both into rock?
答對了
Yeah.
再見
Well, see ya.
你忘了把石英拿走了
Oh, you forgot your quartz.
沒關系
Oh, it's okay.
送給你吧
I want you to have it.
再見
Bye.
他人真好
He's nice.
他對你好是因為他喜歡你
Yeah, he's nice because he likes you.
什么呀  他才不喜歡我呢
What?! No, he doesn't.
他送你一塊漂亮的石頭
He brought you a pretty rock.
那又怎樣  他每天都送我...
So? He does that every day...Oh.
如果你不想吃午飯
You know, if you'd rather skip lunch
而想和你男友伯特在一起  我們完全沒意見
and hang out with your boyfriend Bert, it's totally okay.
他才不是我男朋友呢
He's not my boyfriend.
你確定嗎  他個高  膚白  人怪
Are you sure? He's tall, pale and awkward.
貌似就是你的菜啊
That sounds like your type.
你這種萬年沒人愛的家伙也敢來取笑我嗎
Should someone as lonely as you really be making fun of me?
沒錯  霍華德  你成熟點好不好
Yeah, grow up, Howard. God.
我該怎么做呢  我不想傷害他的感情
What do I do? I don't want to hurt his feelings.
也許問題就出在他不知道你名花有主了
Maybe the problem is he thinks you're available.
他知道你在跟謝爾頓談戀愛嗎
Does he know you're dating Sheldon?
好像從沒提過這事
I guess it hasn't come up.
看吧
There you go.
那謝爾頓知道你們倆是算在談戀愛嗎
And does Sheldon know you're dating Sheldon?
不好意思  那你又是跟誰在戀愛
I'm sorry. Who are you dating?
就是  把嘴閉上  霍華德
Yeah, knock it off, Howard!
謝爾頓
Hey, Sheldon.
你好
Hello.
你沒事吧
You okay?
我在上班  你覺得呢
I'm on vacation. What do you think?
那你為什么坐在樓梯上
Why are you sitting in the stairwell?
萊納德讓我待在這
Leonard told me to stay.
真聽話  乖孩子[狗狗]
Oh. Well, good boy.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
我要出去辦一堆事
Oh, I have a ton of errands to run.
我得去多洗幾張我的大頭照
I need to make copies of my headshot,
寄給不同的經濟人
send them off to agents
然后去報一門新的表演課
and sign up for a new acting class and...
-祝你忙得開心  -好的
- Well, have fun. - Okay.
-你要不要一起來  -可以嗎
- You want to come with me? - Really?
當然可以  走吧  快  乖孩子[狗狗]
Come on, boy. Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
快上車  走
Get in the car. Come on.
謝天謝地
All right, thanks a lot.
首都漫畫店有一本
They have one at Capital Comics.
-那太棒了  -才不是
- Oh, that's great. - No, it's not.
我討厭那地方
I hate that place.
那個店主就是一個混蛋
Guy who owns it is a jerk.
他總愛讓我產生強烈的自卑感
He's always making me feel bad about myself.
太糟糕了
Oh, that's terrible.
那家店在哪里
What's the address?
算了  要不我帶你去吧
You know, why don't I just take you there?
這樣我能確保他不會趁機敲詐
That way, I can make sure he doesn't rip you off.
多謝啦  但我不希望你關門
Oh, thanks, but I don't want you to close up.
你會損失客人的
I mean, won't you lose business?
抱歉  這話太損了
Sorry. That was mean.
-佩妮真的辭掉了服務員的工作嗎  -是的
- Penny really quit The Cheesecake Factory? - Yeah.
-那她今天干什么  -我不知道
- So, what is she doing today? - I don't know.
她已經認為我在這方面不支持她
She already thinks I don't support this,
所以如果我打給她  就會像查崗一樣
so if I call, it might look like I'm checking up on her.
那你支持她嗎
Well, do you support this?
當然支持
Of course I do.
她是一名很棒的女演員
She's a great actress.
她敢冒這個險  真讓我感到驕傲
I'm proud she's taking this risk.
你真貼心
That's nice.
你還真信啊  太棒了
You bought that? Great!
我要在忘記怎么演之前  趕快打給佩妮
I got to call her before I forget how I said it.
怎么了
Hi. What's up?
進展如何
Oh, how's it going?
你有沒有襲卷好萊塢啊
You taking Hollywood by storm?
其實我現在在芝士蛋糕工廠呢
Actually, I'm at The Cheesecake Factory.
你要回工作啦  那真是太好了
You got your job back. That is great news.
我本來不想多說什么
I didn't want to say anything,
但你這么做才是正確的
but you are making the right choice.
現在就切斷自己的經濟來源
To plunge yourself into debt right now
-簡直就是瘋了嘛  -是啊
- would be literally insane. Yeah.
我是來這還工作服的
I'm just returning my uniform.
對了  我支持你哦
And I support you.
在開始接受冥想引導前
Before we begin your guided meditation,
閉上眼
close your eyes
想象自己處于一個平和安詳的環境
and picture yourself in a peaceful environment.
好的
Okay.
我處于歐洲核子研究中心的超級對撞機里
I'm inside the CERN super collider.
現在用鼻子輕松地深吸一口氣
Now, take a deep, relaxing breath in through your nose.
然后呼氣
And let it out.
真是"沒想到"啊
Didn't see that coming.
吸氣
In.
下一步肯定是...
Let me guess.
呼氣
And out.
不然咧  連吸兩口氣憋死自己嗎
What was I gonna do? Two "ins" in a row?
我的檸檬汁呢
Where's my lemonade?
我忘了
I didn't get it.
告別你服務員職業生涯的最佳方式
A fitting swan song to your career as a waitress
就是最后一次忘記我的點單
to forget my order one last time.
你認為我辭職是個錯誤嗎
Do you think quitting my job was a mistake?
你有看到我在喝檸檬汁嗎
Do you see me drinking lemonade?
我是說真的
No. I'm serious.
干嘛這么問
Why do you ask?
因為萊納德剛剛氣到我了
Because Leonard just pissed me off.
我辭職是不是特傻啊
Am I being an idiot or not?
不啊  我不這么認為
No, I don't think you are.
真的嗎
Really?
達到目標的最好辦法就是投入自己
The best way to achieve a goal is to devote 100%
百分之百的時間和精力
of your time and energy to it.
當我決心要成為一個物理學家時
When I decided I was going to be a physicist,
我沒有隨便找一份工作
I didn't take some other job
好給自己留一條后路
in case it didn't work out.
這決定不容易  因為那年皮爾森老師
Which wasn't easy because there was a lot of pressure
不斷對我施壓  讓我當補粉筆專員
from Ms. Pierson for me to be chalk monitor that year.
謝謝  我需要這樣的鼓勵
Thank you. I needed to hear that.
為什么萊納德就是不明白呢
Why can't Leonard understand it?
因為他不像咱倆  佩妮
Because he's not like us, Penny.
我們是夢想家
We're dreamers.
是是  下次再把你留在車里
Yeah, I need to start cracking the window
得留個縫  免得你腦子缺氧了
when I leave you in the car.
你好  伯特
Hello, Bert.
對了  下周在圣塔莫尼卡有個
So, anyway, there's this big, uh, rock and mineral show
大型的巖石礦物展
next week in Santa Monica and...
聽著  伯特
Listen, um, Bert,
在你說出口之前  我想告訴你
before you say anything else, I...
我有男朋友了
I have a boyfriend.
這下尷尬了
This is awkward.
你以為我是邀請你跟我一起
You thought I was gonna ask you to go with me
-去看展覽嗎  -難道不是嗎
to the mineral show. - Weren't you?
是的
Yeah.
多謝你的好意  但
That's very nice of you, but...
我的確有男朋友了
I do have a boyfriend.
你們都這么說
That's what you all say.
你們只是不想跟我出去約會
You just don't want to go out with me
因為我是個令人討厭的人
because I have an off-putting personality.
不  不是的
No, that's not true.
我的男朋友也是一個讓人討厭的人
My boyfriend has an off-putting personality, too.
而且比你討厭多了
Like, way worse than you.
別擔心
Don't worry.
我習慣了
I'm used to it.
我這么大只  個性古怪  長相奇怪
I mean, I'm big and weird and funny-looking
從來不會有人想跟我一起玩
and no one ever wants to do anything with me.
別那樣說
Don't say that.
沒關系
It's okay.
我知道我就是一怪物
I know I'm a monster.
不  伯特  別走
No, Bert, come on.
我很樂意陪你去看礦物展
I'd love to go to the mineral show with you.
太棒了
Sweet.
那就算約會啦
It's a date.
才不算呢
No, it's not.
為時已晚啦
Too late!
自從那輛韓國教堂大巴
Yeah. Haven't seen this many people in my store
從我店前門玻璃撞進來后
since that Korean church bus
我店再也沒有見過那么多人
crashed through my front window.
斯圖爾特
Hey! Stuart!
杰西
Jesse.
好久不見
Haven't seen you in forever.
你看你都灰成這樣了
Look how gray you've gotten.
我的頭發一直都是這個顏色
My hair's exactly the same color as always.
不  我是在說你的膚色
No, I was talking about your skin.
我的朋友要找一本漫畫書
Look, uh, my friend here needs a comic book...
她應該是無意走進你的店吧
And she went into your store by mistake.
幸好他家店沒人  不會有人知道你走錯地方
Good thing there was no one there to see you.
你要找什么
What do you need?
這本啊  我這里有
Oh, yeah, yeah. I got this.
就在這邊
Right over here.
運動褲肥仔  連你也拋棄我
Even you, Sweatpants?
這里有免費爆米花呢
Free popcorn.
要不要來一杯咖啡
Can I offer you a coffee?
是濃縮咖啡還是拿鐵呢
Espresso? Latte?
不用了  謝謝
No, thanks.
你呢  斯圖  摩卡還是司康餅
How about you, Stu? Mocha? Scone?
還是要這附近施舍處的地址啊
Directions to the nearest soup kitchen?
他知道施舍處在哪
He knows where the soup kitchen is.
在默頓大道上
It's on Merton Avenue.
我不喜歡你這樣對待我的朋友
I don't think I like the way you're treating my friend.
抱歉
Sorry.
你還想不想要這本書了
You want the book or not?
想要也不買你的
Not from you.
我們走  斯圖爾特
Let's go, Stuart.
你知道嗎  杰西
You know something, Jesse?
雖說你生意興隆
You may have a successful business
均衡營養
a-and the kind of pink complexion
養得一臉粉嫩
that comes with good nutrition...
但我擁有更重要的東西
...but I have something more important.
是什么
What's that?
友誼
Friendship.
但我會毫不猶豫放棄友誼來換取這一切
Which I would trade in a heartbeat for all of this.
礦物巖石展覽
The mineral and rock show?
即使不跟伯特去  聽著都很沒勁
That would be awful even without Bert.
那我現在應該怎么辦
So what am I supposed to do now?
讓你的子宮為他的巨人嬰兒做好準備
Prepare your uterus for his gigantic offspring?
不許拿這事開玩笑
This isn't funny.
我必須跟他說實話
I'm gonna have to tell him the truth:
就算我沒有男友
that even if I didn't have a boyfriend,
也不會喜歡他
I wouldn't be interested in him.
這話我聽過太多遍了
I've heard those words so many times.
琳達·諾森恰克  譚米·羅森沃塞爾
From Linda Nosenchuck, Tammy Rosenworcel...
帕德瑪·卡普爾  內哈·恰德瑞
Padma Kapur, Neha Chowdury...
馬茜·格羅斯曼  莉薩·馬扎里諾
...Marci Grossman, Lisa Mazzarino...
-梅根·平卡斯  -譚米·周
- ...Megan Pincus... - ...Tammy Cho...
我們常去那家星巴克的女生叫什么來著
Oh, who was that girl from our Starbucks?
-艾琳·羅素  -沒錯  艾琳
- Arlene Russel! - Yes! Arlene!
她在我倆的卡布奇諾杯上  都寫上了"不可能"
She wrote "no way" on both our cappuccinos.
可憐的伯特
Poor Bert.
有一個悲催的下午在等著他
That guy's got a rough afternoon ahead of him.
你們希望一個女生
Well, how would you want a girl
如何拒絕你們
to tell you she wasn't interested?
我希望她和我好好坐著
I guess, uh, I'd like her to sit me down,
看著我的眼睛說
look me in the eye and say,
"我錯了  我愛你"
"I was wrong. I love you."
或許再用上特別的方式愛撫我
And then maybe she could touch me in a special way.
沒錯  拒絕男生就要這樣
That's how you reject a guy.
我沒時間聽你倆瞎掰
Okay, I don't have time for this.
我要直接去找他  殘忍地說出真相算了
I'm just gonna go find him and be brutally honest.
-別這樣  -他會很傷心的
- No, don't. - He'll be so upset.
他很可能會爬上帝國大廈
He'll probably climb up the Empire State Building
像電影里的金剛一樣亂拍飛機泄憤
and start swatting at planes.
要我們幫你說嗎
You want us to talk to him?
可以嗎
Really?
-你們愿意代勞嗎  -當然
- You would do that? - Sure.
我們都曾有過這樣的經歷
We've both been in his shoes.
我們會讓他失望的同時  感覺到同情與尊重
We'll let him down with compassion and respect.
謝謝
Thank you.
我們走
Let's go.
跟他說她是拉拉嗎
So we tell him she's a lesbian, right?
當然是說她是拉拉啦
Of course we tell him she's a lesbian.
保持三
And hold three...
二  一
two... one.
非常好
Very good.
現在試試戰士二式
Now let's try Warrior II.
保持
And hold.
有報道指出有些偉大的瑜伽修行者
I've read that there are great yogis
可以隨心所欲掌控自己的身體
who have such mastery over their bodies
他們能通過生殖器汲水
they can draw water in through their genitals.
我們今天還不會練到這一層次
Yeah, well, I don't think we're gonna get to do that today.
太遺憾了
Too bad.
感覺用這種辦法喝奶昔不錯
It seems like a good way to drink a milk shake
至少大腦不會冰到痛
without getting brain freeze.
現在是反轉戰士式
And now we go to Reverse Warrior.
她是怎么說服你做瑜伽的
How did she get you to do yoga?
說實話  我以為她說的是"尤達"
Well, to be honest, I thought she said "Yoda."
《星戰》里的大師  音似瑜伽
我在幫他放松  因為他和你不同
I'm helping him relax because, unlike you,
他支持我
he supports me.
究竟要我說多少次啊
Oh, how many times do I have to say it?
我支持你
I support you.
謝爾頓  休息下
Sheldon, take a break.
合十致敬
Namaste.
如果你支持我  那通電話是什么意思
Okay, if you support me, what was with that phone call?
好吧  我不確定你是否該辭職
Fine. I'm not sure you should have quit.
但如果你這么在乎我的想法
But if you care so much what I think,
你為什么不在辭職前問我呢
why didn't you ask me before you did it?
所以現在我做事需要你的批準嗎
Oh, so now I need your permission?
你在辭職前會征求我的意見嗎
Would you have asked me before you quit your job?
當然會
Yes.
我覺得我們的關系已經到了
I thought we were in the kind of relationship
什么事都一起做決定的階段
where we make decisions together.
如果我錯了  那也許我們應該談談
If I'm wrong, then maybe we need to talk about
我們的關系究竟在哪一階段
the kind of relationship we're actually in.
也許是需要談談了
Yeah, well, maybe we do.
你們想談的話  我也很樂意談
I'm willing to if you guys are.
給我們一些空間好嗎
Can we please have some privacy?
不行
Y... No.
除了你們倆  我也是這段關系的一名成員
I'm as much a part of this relationship as you two,
我覺得是時候大家把話說開了
and I think it's high time we put all our cards on the table.
比如  這段感情的未來在哪里
Yeah. For example, where is this going?
你們到底會不會結婚
Are you two ever getting married?
還有婚后  我們仨要住在哪里
And, if so, where will we all live?
你們有考慮這個問題嗎
Have you thought about that?
-沒有  -佩妮呢
- No. - Penny?
慢著  我們這是在干嘛
Okay, wait. What are we doing?
不知為何  我們現在談的是
For some reason, we're planning a future
我們與謝爾頓永遠住在一起的未來
where we both live with Sheldon forever.
很好  總算有點進展了
Good. Now we're getting somewhere.
我知道你覺得我太過魯莽
Look, I know you think I'm being reckless,
也許你是對的
and you might be right,
但我需要把握這次機會
but I need to take this shot.
對  這是說真的
Yeah, no kidding.
盡管她在簡歷上造假
Despite what it says on her resume,
她早就不是22歲了
she is no longer 22.
我發誓  我向來支持你
I swear, I am on your side.
你總是口頭上說支持我
You keep saying you're on my side,
-而你的言行完全不一致  -他對我也是這樣
- but you don't act like it. - He does that to me, too.
我們為什么要容忍你這種行為
Why do we put up with it?
聽我說  我永遠做不到你現在做的事
Listen, I could never do what you're doing, okay?
我沒這么大膽
I would be terrified.
其實我心里也很害怕
Well, it's scary for me, too.
我還好啦
I'm fine with it.
我的意思是  不能因為我做不到
My point is, just because I couldn't do it
就代表你不應該去做
doesn't mean you shouldn't.
我為你驕傲
And I'm proud of you.
好的  謝謝
Okay. Thank you.
為了慶祝重歸于好
Well, to celebrate this reconciliation,
咱們分享一杯奶昔吧
let's all share a milk shake.
佩妮  你用吸管  我們"龍汲水"
Uh, Penny, you'll need a straw.
-你還是回來了  -是的
- You're back. - Yes, I am!
我還有一些話要對你說
There's a few more things I want to say to you.
斯圖爾特的店挺好的
Stuart's store is just fine,
而且他人也比你好多了
and he's a much nicer person than you are,
如果那本漫畫書還在
and if you still have that comic,
我現在就想買
I'd like to buy it right now!
沒問題
No problem.
等的時候要來杯拿鐵嗎
Oh, you want a latte while you wait?
不  我才不要拿鐵
No, I don't want a latte!
我要卡布奇諾和藍莓司康餅
I want a cappuccino and a blueberry scone!
我這里只有巧克力曲奇餅
I only have chocolate chip.
這更符合姐心意
Well, that sounds even better!
多謝你們陪我去看礦物巖石展
Thanks for coming to the mineral and rock show with me.
很抱歉艾米不想去
We're sorry Amy didn't want to go.
我們真的深感抱歉[后悔]
Really, really sorry.
有你們陪我  還要她干嘛
Who needs her when I have you guys?
巖石展覽
Rock show!
巖石展覽  巖石展覽
Rock show! Rock show!
巖石展覽
Rock show!
Rock show...!